owclb.com 2012-12-27

# OWCLB.COM Privacy Policy

****Older Women Club**** recognizes that its customers, visitors, users, and others who use ****Older Women Club**** value their privacy. This privacy notice details important information regarding the use and disclosure of user information collected on the ****Older Women Club**** site. We provide this privacy notice to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using our site.

The Information Older Women Club Collects:

User-provided information: You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to ****Older Women Club**** when choosing to participate in various activities on the sites such as posting messages.

Cookies Information: When you visit the ****Older Women Club**** site, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. ****Older Women Club**** uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the ****Older Women Club**** site may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

Log File Information: When you use the ****Older Women Club**** site, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Inte  
et Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser

The Way ****Older Women Club**** Limited Uses Information:

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the ****Older Women Club**** website, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the site.

Any personal information that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other users when you send messages through the ****Older Women Club**** site, and other users can contact you through messages and comments.

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes.

We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant.

****Older Women Club**** also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our terms of use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist govement enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of our company, our users or others.

Our Commitment to Legal-Age Usage:

Protecting children from adult content is especially important. For that reason, ****Older Women Club**** does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the ****Older Women Club**** site from persons under 18 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 18, or legal age according to state law. If you are under 18 years of age, then please do not use or access the ****Older Women Club**** site at any time or in any manner.

Changes and updates to this Privacy Notice:

This privacy notice may be revised periodically and users are encouraged to review it periodically to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of the ****Older Women Club**** site constitutes your agreement to this privacy notice and any future revisions.
